export const music = {
  finishLyric: [
    { id: 'fl1', song: "Mr. Brightside - The Killers", lyrics: "Jealousy, turning saints into the sea...", answer: "Swimming through sick lullabies" },
    { id: 'fl2', song: "Bad Romance - Lady Gaga", lyrics: "I want your love and I want your revenge...", answer: "You and me could write a bad romance" },
    { id: 'fl3', song: "Espresso - Sabrina Carpenter", lyrics: "That's that me...", answer: "Espresso" },
    { id: 'fl4', song: "Cruel Summer - Taylor Swift", lyrics: "Devils roll the dice, angels roll their eyes...", answer: "What doesn't kill me makes me want you more" },
    { id: 'fl5', song: "Bohemian Rhapsody - Queen", lyrics: "Is this the real life? Is this just fantasy?...", answer: "Caught in a landslide, no escape from reality" },
    { id: 'fl6', song: "Wonderwall - Oasis", lyrics: "Today is gonna be the day...", answer: "That they're gonna throw it back to you" },
    { id: 'fl7', song: "Someone Like You - Adele", lyrics: "Never mind, I'll find...", answer: "Someone like you" },
    { id: 'fl8', song: "As It Was - Harry Styles", lyrics: "You know it's not the same as it was...", answer: "In this world, it's just us" },
    { id: 'fl9', song: "Anti-Hero - Taylor Swift", lyrics: "It's me, hi...", answer: "I'm the problem, it's me" },
    { id: 'fl10', song: "Vampire - Olivia Rodrigo", lyrics: "Bloodsucker, fame f*cker...", answer: "Bleeding me dry like a goddamn vampire" },
    { id: 'fl11', song: "Flowers - Miley Cyrus", lyrics: "I can buy myself flowers...", answer: "Write my name in the sand" },
    { id: 'fl12', song: "Say My Name - Destiny's Child", lyrics: "Say my name, say my name...", answer: "If no one is around you, say baby I love you" }
  ],
  whoSings: [
    { id: 'ws1', question: "Who sings 'Uptown Funk'?", answer: "Mark Ronson ft. Bruno Mars", options: ["Justin Timberlake", "Mark Ronson ft. Bruno Mars", "Pharrell Williams", "The Weeknd"] },
    { id: 'ws2', question: "Who sings 'Shape of You'?", answer: "Ed Sheeran", options: ["Sam Smith", "Ed Sheeran", "Shawn Mendes", "James Arthur"] },
    { id: 'ws3', question: "Who sings 'Rolling in the Deep'?", answer: "Adele", options: ["Amy Winehouse", "Adele", "Dua Lipa", "Jessie J"] },
    { id: 'ws4', question: "Who sings 'Blinding Lights'?", answer: "The Weeknd", options: ["Drake", "The Weeknd", "Bruno Mars", "Post Malone"] },
    { id: 'ws5', question: "Who sings 'Shake It Off'?", answer: "Taylor Swift", options: ["Katy Perry", "Taylor Swift", "Ariana Grande", "Selena Gomez"] },
    { id: 'ws6', question: "Who sings 'Levitating'?", answer: "Dua Lipa", options: ["Doja Cat", "Dua Lipa", "Charli XCX", "Bebe Rexha"] },
    { id: 'ws7', question: "Who sings 'Peaches'?", answer: "Justin Bieber ft. Daniel Caesar & Giveon", options: ["Drake", "The Weeknd", "Justin Bieber", "Bruno Mars"] },
    { id: 'ws8', question: "Who sings 'Good 4 U'?", answer: "Olivia Rodrigo", options: ["Billie Eilish", "Olivia Rodrigo", "Sabrina Carpenter", "Tate McRae"] },
    { id: 'ws9', question: "Who sings 'Watermelon Sugar'?", answer: "Harry Styles", options: ["Niall Horan", "Harry Styles", "Liam Payne", "Louis Tomlinson"] },
    { id: 'ws10', question: "Who sings 'Espresso'?", answer: "Sabrina Carpenter", options: ["Olivia Rodrigo", "Tate McRae", "Sabrina Carpenter", "Chappell Roan"] },
    { id: 'ws11', question: "Who sings 'Not Like Us'?", answer: "Kendrick Lamar", options: ["Drake", "Kendrick Lamar", "J. Cole", "Travis Scott"] },
    { id: 'ws12', question: "Who sings 'Birds of a Feather'?", answer: "Billie Eilish", options: ["Olivia Rodrigo", "Billie Eilish", "Lorde", "Chappell Roan"] }
  ],
  grabMic: [
    { id: 'gm1', song: "Sweet Caroline", artist: "Neil Diamond", chorus: "Sweet Caroline! Ba ba ba!" },
    { id: 'gm2', song: "Don't Stop Believin'", artist: "Journey", chorus: "Don't stop believin', hold on to that feelin'" },
    { id: 'gm3', song: "Living on a Prayer", artist: "Bon Jovi", chorus: "Whoa, we're halfway there, whoa-oh, livin' on a prayer" },
    { id: 'gm4', song: "I Will Survive", artist: "Gloria Gaynor", chorus: "I will survive! Oh, as long as I know how to love, I know I'll stay alive" },
    { id: 'gm5', song: "Wannabe", artist: "Spice Girls", chorus: "If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends" },
    { id: 'gm6', song: "Dancing Queen", artist: "ABBA", chorus: "Dancing Queen, young and sweet, only seventeen" },
    { id: 'gm7', song: "Mr. Brightside", artist: "The Killers", chorus: "Jealousy, turning saints into the sea" },
    { id: 'gm8', song: "Summer of '69", artist: "Bryan Adams", chorus: "Those were the best days of my life" },
    { id: 'gm9', song: "Piano Man", artist: "Billy Joel", chorus: "La la la, di da da" },
    { id: 'gm10', song: "Livin' La Vida Loca", artist: "Ricky Martin", chorus: "Livin' la vida loca, she's livin' la vida loca" }
  ],
  albumTrivia: [
    { id: 'at1', question: "Which Taylor Swift album has a track list that spells out 'YEAR OF THE SNAKE' in secret messages?", answer: "Reputation (2017)", context: "Snake imagery everywhere!" },
    { id: 'at2', question: "What is the best-selling album of all time?", answer: "Thriller by Michael Jackson", context: "Over 70 million copies sold worldwide" },
    { id: 'at3', question: "Which Beatles album features the iconic zebra crossing cover?", answer: "Abbey Road", context: "The last album they recorded together" },
    { id: 'at4', question: "Which album won the most Grammys in a single night (5)?", answer: "1989 by Taylor Swift", context: "Album of the Year among them" },
    { id: 'at5', question: "Which Drake album title references his hometown's area code?", answer: "Views", context: "416 is Toronto's area code - VIEWS = 416" },
    { id: 'at6', question: "Which Pink Floyd album features a prism on the cover?", answer: "The Dark Side of the Moon", context: "One of the best-selling albums ever" },
    { id: 'at7', question: "Which album's title is also a color and sold the most copies in 2011?", answer: "21 by Adele", context: "Her age when she started writing it" },
    { id: 'at8', question: "Which Nirvana album features a naked baby swimming after a dollar?", answer: "Nevermind", context: "That baby is now in his 30s!" },
    { id: 'at9', question: "Which Beyoncé surprise album dropped at midnight with no promotion?", answer: "Beyoncé (self-titled)", context: "Changed the music industry release model" },
    { id: 'at10', question: "Which Kanye West album has no cover art - just a plain orange square?", answer: "Jesus Is King", context: "Released in 2019" }
  ],
  musicHistory: [
    { id: 'mh1', question: "Which music streaming service launched in 2008 and changed how we listen to music?", answer: "Spotify", context: "Founded in Sweden" },
    { id: 'mh2', question: "What was the first music video played on MTV?", answer: "Video Killed the Radio Star by The Buggles", context: "August 1, 1981" },
    { id: 'mh3', question: "Which festival is known as the 'Woodstock of the 90s'?", answer: "Lollapalooza", context: "Started by Perry Farrell of Jane's Addiction" },
    { id: 'mh4', question: "What year did Apple launch iTunes?", answer: "2001", context: "Changed digital music forever" },
    { id: 'mh5', question: "Which British band has the most #1 singles in UK chart history?", answer: "The Beatles", context: "17 number one singles" },
    { id: 'mh6', question: "Which artist performed the most-watched Super Bowl halftime show ever?", answer: "Katy Perry (2015)", context: "118.5 million viewers" },
    { id: 'mh7', question: "What was the first song to reach 1 billion streams on Spotify?", answer: "One Dance by Drake", context: "December 2016" },
    { id: 'mh8', question: "Which female artist has the most Grammy wins of all time?", answer: "Beyoncé", context: "32 Grammys as of 2024" },
    { id: 'mh9', question: "Which K-pop group was the first to perform at Coachella?", answer: "BLACKPINK", context: "2019, then headlined in 2023" },
    { id: 'mh10', question: "Which legendary club in Liverpool is where The Beatles got their start?", answer: "The Cavern Club", context: "292 performances between 1961-1963" }
  ],
  guessTheYear: [
    { id: 'gy1', question: "In what year did Britney Spears release '...Baby One More Time'?", answer: "1998" },
    { id: 'gy2', question: "In what year did Adele release 'Hello'?", answer: "2015" },
    { id: 'gy3', question: "In what year did Ed Sheeran release 'Shape of You'?", answer: "2017" },
    { id: 'gy4', question: "In what year did Billie Eilish release 'Bad Guy'?", answer: "2019" },
    { id: 'gy5', question: "In what year did One Direction form on X Factor?", answer: "2010" },
    { id: 'gy6', question: "In what year did Amy Winehouse release 'Back to Black'?", answer: "2006" },
    { id: 'gy7', question: "In what year did 'Gangnam Style' go viral?", answer: "2012" },
    { id: 'gy8', question: "In what year did Taylor Swift release her first album?", answer: "2006" },
    { id: 'gy9', question: "In what year did Beyoncé go solo with 'Crazy in Love'?", answer: "2003" },
    { id: 'gy10', question: "In what year did The Weeknd release 'Blinding Lights'?", answer: "2019" }
  ]
}

export default music
